(捷克布拉格帕里斯卡血库)
第一次卖血?
First time giving blood?
对
Yes.
他们付现金
They pay cash here.
也不管你卖过多少次
And there's no limit to how many times you give.
连瓶装的都肯买
They even buy it in the jar.
查德诺玛 轮到你了
Jared Nomak, we're ready for you.
过去一年内有没有...
In the past 12 months, have you gotten a tattoo...
...刺青或其他刺穿皮肤举动?
...or undergone any ear, skin, or body piercings?
没有
No.
你下巴的疤是怎么回事?
Where did you get that scar on your chin?
小时候出过意外
Childhood accident.
你说你没有任何近亲 对不?
You say you don't have any immediate next of kin, is that right?
至少没跟任何近亲连络
Not that I'm in contact with.
- 万一有紧急事故没人可连络?  - 一个都没有
- Nobody to call in case of an emergency?  - No one.
没有家人? 跟你说过 没有
No family? I told you, no.
你是说我不能捐血?
Are you telling me I can't be a donor?
不一定 你的验血结果不寻常
It depends. We came up with some unusual results on your blood test.
什么? 多不寻常?
What? How? How unusual?
我来解释
Let me explain.
你血液中含有稀有的显型体 我们从未见过
Your blood has a very rare phenotype, one we haven't encountered before.
什么? 你在说什么?
What? What are you talking about?
- 你们是谁? 不 不  - 请坐下
- Who are you? No. No.  - Sit down, please.
这是怎么回事?
What is this?
这是好坏参半的局面 查德
This is a good news-bad news scenario, Jared.
对我们是好事
Good news for us.
却是坏事...
Bad news...
...对你
...for you.
一群吸血鬼!
我最恨吸血鬼
忘掉你们自以为了解的想法
Forget what you think you know.
吸血鬼确实存在
Vampires exist.
本人刀锋战士
My name is Blade.
天生半人半吸血鬼
I was born half human, half vampire.
其他吸血鬼叫我白昼游侠
They call me The Deywelker.
我拥有他们的力量 却没有他们的弱点...
I have all their strengths, none of their weaknesses...
...除了同样嗜血如命
...except for the thirst.
二十年前 一个人改变了我
Twenty years ago, I met a man that changed that.
惠斯勒
Whistler.
他教我如何控制嗜血的冲动
He taught me how to hold the thirst at bay.
教我狩猎法则
Taught me the rules.
也给了我狩猎工具:
Gave me the weapons to hunt with:
银器 大蒜 阳光
Silver, garlic, sunlight.
二年前 他遭到攻击
Two years ago, he was attacked.
被逮去变成我最恨的东西
They took him, and turned him into the thing I hate most.
我早该了结他的生命
I should have finished him off.
现在 我正在猎捕他
Now I'm hunting him.
我一定会找到他
I will find him.
什么都阻挡不了我
And nothing will stand in my way.
《刀锋战士2》
白昼游侠来了! 拦住他!
Daywalker's here! Stop him!
他在哪里?
Where is he?
去他妈的!
嘿!
Hey!
不要 不要
No, no.
不知道他们将他藏在哪里
带我去找他 我放你一马
Take me to him, and I'll consider you a loose end.
拜托  我不知道
他举枪自杀变成吸血鬼
我们只是维持他的性命!
我带你去! 我带你去!
我是罗许 让我进去
不要开枪! 是我!
干!不是银的但痛得要命
待会再收拾你
Catch you later.
老头
Old man.
看他们怎么对待你
Look at what they've done to you.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
看紧你们的女儿 黑骑士来了
Lock up your daughters, boys and girls, the dark knight returns.
- 哈一管吗, 刀兄?  - 待会
- Need a toke of the smokage there, B?  - Later.
灯关掉
Cut the lights.
你找到他了
You found him.
你没干掉他
You didn't kill him.
帮个忙
Give me a hand.
我觉得不妙 刀兄
I got a bad feeling about this, B.
听他的呼吸 他快挂了
Unh! Listen to his breathing. He's already dying.
他很痛苦 不如给他个痛快?
He's in pain. Why don't you just put him out of his misery?
他们将他滞留在变身剂中
They had him on stasis in a halfway house.
我要为他加速逆转解毒
I'm giving him an accelerated retro-viral detox.
就好像戒海洛因瘾
Like a heroin addict.
- 啊!  - 让他一夜就恢复正常
- Agh!  - Make him go cold turkey in one night.
妈的没用的 老兄
Shit ain't gonna work, man.
我建议杀了这王八蛋
I say you kill the motherfucker right now.
出去
Get out.
不管有没有东西残留你体内 惠斯勒 听好
If there's anything left of you in there, Whistler, listen up.
明天一早 我会拉开窗帘...
In the morning, those blinds are going to open...
...不管你复原了没
...whether you're cured or not.
老兄 我不是有意…
Hey, man, I didn't mean to call him...
听我说 刀锋战士
Listen to me, Blade.
- 你必须把我干掉  - 不
- You're gonna have to finish me off.  - No.
枪给我
Give me that damn gun.
走开
Now walk away.
你这个傻小子
Stubborn son of a bitch.
感觉如何?
How do you feel?
好像被毒打了一顿
Like hammered shit.
你怎么找到我的?
How'd you find me?
从莫斯科开始 然后罗马尼亚
Started out in Moscow, then Romania.
- 他们不断将你藏在不同地方  - 我消失了多久?
- They kept moving you around.  - How long was I gone?
- 好几个月?  - 非常久
- Months?  - Too long.
好几年
Years.
他们把我折磨得半死...
They'd torture me almost to death...
...然后丢在血桶里治疗...
...and then let me heal in a vat of blood...
...以便再折磨我一次
...so they could go at it again.
那些混蛋也不顺便医好我的脚
Sorry sons of bitches could have at least fixed my goddamn leg while they were at it.
我的高压焊枪呢?
Where's my arc welder?
惠斯勒 幸会 久仰大名
Whistler, nice to meet you, man. I heard a lot about you.
我叫乔许 外号人称飞毛腿
I'm Josh. You can call me Scud, though. Everybody does.
我问你 毛毛腿
Tell me something, Skid.
不 是飞毛腿 类似千里马
No, man, it's Scud. Scud, like "stud."
- 飞毛腿  - 随便啦 你在这里干嘛?
- Scud.  - Whatever. What did you do in here?
你是说这辆酷车? 做点个性化改装
The pimpmobile? Just a little after-market modification.
- 二氧化氮燃料之类的  - 是的
- Nitrous oxide and shit like that.  - Oh, yeah.
你想改良排气系统加大马力
You gave it a more aggressive exhaust profile ramping.
全套改装后马力直逼300匹
Whole package will crank that Betty up maybe 300 horsepower.
不到下次换机油引擎就缩缸了
You'll burn the damned thing out before your next oil change.
这屎蛋你哪里找来的?
Where did you dig up this shitbird, anyway?
你哪里不爽 老头?
What the fuck is your problem, Poppy?
我他妈吸了两年血块
My problem is l've been sucking blood clots for two years.
好不容易脱身却看到个猪头 瞎整我毕生的结晶
I get out to find some jerkoff fucking with my life's work.
荒废我们的业务专心伺候你
We jeopardized our operation to save your ass.
- 我们的业务?  - 是的
- "Our operation"?  - Yeah.
我们的? 我一手建立的 废人
"Our operation"? I built this operation, you ass-wipe.
警报系统 第三区 先生
Motion sensors. It's on three, gentlemen.
人类吗?
Human?
体温50度 应该是吸血鬼
Uh, body temperature, 50. I'd guess suckhead.
烧坏了 他们用镁光枪
Fried. They're using magnesium flares.
你的保全系统被破解了
They've got your security system scoped out.
哇喔 哇喔 哇喔 我信不过你…
Whoa. whoa. whoa, I don't trust you...
该死!
Shit!
哇喔 哇喔 哇喔...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
衣服很炫哟
Cool outfit.
打开上帝灯
Guard lights.
妮莎! 把剑拿开
你的人先开火的
我们是来送口信的
我们是吸血鬼执政党的代表
We represent the ruling body of the Vampire Nation.
他们希望跟你谈休战协定
They're offering you a truce.
期待跟你见个面
They want to meet with you.
飞毛腿
Scud.
面罩拿下来
Take off your mask.
我叫亚萨 这位是妮莎
My name is Asad. This is Nyssa.
你是我们最敬畏的敌人
You have been our most feared enemy.
但近来外面有个家伙胆大妄为
But now there's something else loose on the streets.
比你还可怕
Something worse than you.
有什么好笑?
What's so funny?
外面传言刀锋战士有多吓人
They tell stories about Blade as the bogeyman.
老实说 我有点失望
Frankly, I'm disappointed.
听到了没 刀兄? 她很失望
You hear that, B? She's disappointed.
两三下就答应跟我们走
He agreed to come along so easily.
你的宝贝让她瞧瞧 拜托?
Come on, B, show her. Pretty please?
桑坦克斯
Semtex.
足够夷平整条街
Enough explosives to level a city block.
还失望吗?
You still disappointed?
警卫看起来像人 刀兄 可能是冥族
The guards look human, B. They're probably familiars.
你不后悔?
You sure about this?
如果有什么不对劲?
What if I'm not?
吸血鬼帝国的真正力量在此地
The true power of the Vampire Nation lies here.
爸爸?
Father?
刀锋战士 这位是至高大公 艾里大·马基诺斯
Blade, this is Overlord Eli Damaskinos.
白昼游侠 欢迎
常言道 "以敌人为荣 坐享他的成就"
It has been said, "Be proud of your enemy and enjoy his success."
如此看来 我该感谢你
In that regard, I should thank you.
- 怎么说?  - 替我们除掉戴肯·佛洛斯
- For what?  - Eliminating Deacon Frost.
帮个忙 凯洛·酷南
You did us a favor. Karel Kounen.
- 你是人类  - 差一点点 我是律师
- You're human.  - Barely. I'm a lawyer.
欧洲保健国际财团法人
European Health Consortium.
如你所知 吸血习性是一种传染性病毒
As you may know, vampirism is a horrible virus...
...透过掠食者唾液散播
...carried in the saliva of predators.
病毒72小时内流遍人体血管...
In 72 hours, it spreads through the human bloodstream...
...繁衍出寄生性组织
...creating new parasitic organs.
有如癌细胞
Like cancer.
具目的性的癌细胞
Cancer with a purpose.
不幸 病毒也会进化 我们已经发现新进化种
Unfortunately, viruses evolve too. We've encountered a new one.
命名为"R异体"
We dubbed it the Reaper strain.
跟所有优良病原体一样 它迅速找到带原者
And like any good pathogen, it appears to have found a carrier.
就是他 查德·诺玛
There, Jared Nomak.
天生吸血鬼 但跟你一样是异种
Born a vampire, but an anomaly like you.
不像我们其他人 然而...
Unlike the rest of us, however...
...他不但吸食人类 也可以靠吸血鬼维生
...he feeds on not just humans, but vampires as well.
- 看来他是在帮我忙  - 你没听清楚重点
- Looks like he was doing me a favor.  - You're missing the point.
被吸食的吸血鬼不会死
Their vampire victims don't die.
他们转而变成带原者
They turn. They become carriers.
你要知道
You've got to understand.
他们像中快克瘾 他们得天天满足瘾头
These things are like crack addicts. They need to feed daily.
诺玛已经现身72小时了
Nomak's been up for 72 hours.
据我们估计已有打上R异体
By our estimates, there are already a dozen Reapers.
本周结束前会有数百个
There'll be hundreds before the week is out.
几个月后数千人 算算看
Thousands within a matter of months. Do the math.
等等 我先弄清楚
Wait, let me get this right.
你要我为你猎捕他?
You want me to hunt them for you?
对付完我们后 你想他会找上谁?
When they are finished with us, who do you think they'll turn on next?
你珍贵的人类?
Your precious humans.
一个也不能幸免
Not one of them will be left.
两年来我们训练一个战术小组"护血队"
We spent two years training a small tactical unit, the Bloodpack.
希望你来领导他们
We want you to lead them.
两年?
Two years?
本来是训练来猎杀你的
We've been training to hunt you.
- 刀兄 你认为如何?  - 听起来计划还不错
- So, B-man, what do you think?  - Sounds like a plan.
那你的真正想法呢?
What do you really think?
一有机会他们就会反咬我一口
They're gonna fuck us the first chance they get.
所以我们不答应 对吧?
We ain't gonna do this, though, right?
先陪他们玩玩
We'll play along for now.
我们可以深入他们的组织
They'll take us in deeper than we've ever been.
利用机会了解他们的运作
Get a chance to see how their world really ticks.
我已经够了解他们了
I had enough of their world.
他们已经屁滚尿流 食物链顶层的地位不保
They're just shitting bricks because they're no longer top of the food chain.
靠 我很担心他
Damn, man, I'm really worried about him.
他是你朋友 但还是得留心
Look, I know he's your friend and all, but I think you should watch him.
没有人一夜就能恢复正常
Nobody goes cold turkey from the thirst in just one night.
想舒畅舒畅吗?
Looking to get hooked up?
看看罗 你有什么好货?
Maybe. What do you have?
没问题 海洛因 夏威夷极品
No problem. Horse, Hawaiian ice.
要什么有什么
Whatever you need.
Whatever I need.
好极了 如果我要你呢?
I like that. What if I need you?
好甜
So, so sweet.
他们随时待命 白昼游侠
They are ready whenever you are, Daywalker.
刀锋战士 跟护血队见个面
Blade, meet the Bloodpack.
光斧 魏莲...
Lighthammer, Verlaine...
...教士 雪人...
...Priest, Snowman...
...丘巴以及雷哈特
...Chupa and Reinhardt.
嘿
Hey, uh.
我们这夥人很怀疑...
Me and the gang were wondering....
什么事?
What was that?
你会不会脸红?
Can you blush?
帅哦 老爹
Here we go, Poppy.
哦 我懂了
Oh, I get it.
我懂你的意思
I see now.
你们受训两年 目的要作掉我
You've been training for two years to take me out.
没想到却变成这局面
And now here I am.
哦
Ooh.
哦 很爽 对吧?
Ooh, so exciting, isn't it?
好 给你们一个机会
Okay, here's your chance.
来啊 上啊 等什么?
Come on. Come on, what are you waiting for?
我就在你们面前
Here I am, right here in front of you.
希特勒 你先上
Adolf here gets the first shot.
上啊 看她干嘛? 要她批准吗?
Come on. What are you looking at her for? You need permission?
需要奖励吗 好 我可以帮个忙
Maybe you need a little bit of incentive. Okay, I can help with that.
怎么回事? 打不到?
What's the matter? Missed that?
好吧 再来一次
It's okay, I can do it again.
加油 雷哈特 要操作手册吗?
Come on. What, you need a manual?
- 干掉他!  - 上啊! 干掉他!
- Kill the bastard!  - Do it! Come on!
现在你后脑挂了一个爆裂物
Now you've got an explosive device stuck to the back of your head.
硝酸银 谁敢碰它 它就会炸开
Silver nitrate, rigged to go off if anybody tampers with it.
我随身带着引信
I'll have the detonator with me.
你 如果看我不顺眼...
And you, if you so much as look at me wrong...
哇哦
Whoo.
现在开始 我们并肩作战
From now on, we work as a unit.
你们得听我的命令行事
You'll be taking orders from me.
有问题吗?
Any questions?
很好
Good.
要抓猎人先从猎物下手
You want to catch the hunter, you start with the prey.
目标摆在吸血鬼夜间聚集地
We'll target all the night places where vampires congregate.
血库 巢穴 越大越好
Blood banks, safe houses, the bigger, the better.
哪里是第一个目标?
So, what's first?
痛苦之屋
The House of Pain.
入口在哪里?
Where's the entrance?
没招牌 没吸血鬼雕像
I don't see any signs, no vampire glyphs.
没有 因为你我们得改变习惯...
No, because of you, we've had to rethink our habits...
...加强安全措施
...tighten our security.
仔细搜索
Have a closer look.
好极了
Nice.
38 .45跟9厘米的
Thirty-eight, .45 and 9mm caliber.
尖端都有个小胶囊 里面是硝酸银和大蒜萃取物
All with foil capsules at the tip filled with silver nitrate and garlic extract.
这把高速箭枪 射出的银箭速度达每秒六千尺
This hyper-velocity stake gun spits out a silver stake at 6000 feet per second.
由于你们害怕阳光...
Since you suckers don't like sunlight...
...瞄准仪特别加装了紫外线滤镜
...we've modified the gun's entry light with a UV filter.
滤镜打开 立刻射出紫外线
Pop it open, instant UV light.
- 盖上滤镜则无杀伤力  - 刀兄 你看看这玩意
- Filter's on, no problem.  - Yo, B, check this out.
它装有气压注射系统
It's got a pneumatic syringe delivery system.
药瓶内装的是EDTA抗凝血剂
The vials are filled with an anticoagulant called EDTA.
打一针 目标立刻涨得像气球
One punch with this blows your target up like a balloon.
弹匣跳出 自动重新上膛
The cartridge ejects. Automatic reload.
正点
Nice.
走吧
Let's go.
我们没有人相信你
You won't pass for one of us. No way.
- 希罕  - 不 他说得没错
- Like I give a shit.  - No, he's right.
你为什么不到屋顶上去?
Why don't you post up on the roof over there?
掩护我们
Cover our backs.
看来由护血队发号施令啦?
So the Bloodpack's calling the shots now, huh?
太好了
Great.
狗儿管好 不然我替你管教
Better curb that dog of yours or we'll do it for you.
你想找死 白痴
Keep pushing, asshole.
我们进来了
We're in.
你即将进入我们的世界
You're about to enter our world.
会看到一些事情 比如说进食
You will see things, feeding.
记住你来此的目的
Just remember why you're here.
我没有忘记
I haven't forgotten.
我们来这里找什么?
What exactly are we looking for in here?
任何可疑的东西
Anything that looks suspicious.
开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
∮ 你们怎么得到猎人 叫我看看你们的欲望 ∮
∮ What y'all get it ain't haunted, call it I see some of y'all thirsty for it. ∮
∮ 直接针对你们战斗 狗 我是工作狂 ∮
∮ Straight frontin'y'all winnin'come down To the combat, dog, I'm a workaholic. ∮
∮ 在我的扳机下射杀所有敌人 ∮
∮ My swag touches every enemy Within my clutches. ∮
∮ 刀锋制造威胁 就要靠你所了解的 ∮
∮ Black makin'that ruckus And I'm puttin'that lean on all you suckas. ∮
∮ 刀锋! 你的力量压垮所有对手 ∮
∮ Black! Your bone crushes Every opponent suffers. ∮
∮ 你不喜欢打击对手? ∮
∮ Your tone hushes from punches Don't you like percussion? ∮
∮ 不要失去你的生活 ∮
∮ Don't lose yo life for nothin'. ∮
∮ 你不想去接触它们 ∮
∮ You don't wanna try to touch 'em. ∮
∮ 没有竞争 听着 这不是公开讨论 ∮
∮ No competition, listen This ain't open for discussion. ∮
∮ 你想要它 希望它来 你想要它 ∮
∮ He, you want it, want it Come on, you want it. ∮
∮ 你想要它那就来吧 哈哈 ∮
∮ Ha, come on, you want it, want it. Ha, you want it, come on. ∮
飞毛腿 听到请回答?
Scud, do you read me?
- 能看到我吗?  - 非常清楚 刀兄
- You reading me?  - Reading you loud and clear, B.
这是个大巢穴
The whole place is a safe house.
窗户漆黑 有道逃生门
Windows are painted black, one access door.
- 二 三百个吸血鬼在这里  - 酷毙了
- Two-or 300 suckheads in here.  - That sounds cool.
嘿 老惠 听得到吗?
Hey, W, you got me?
老惠?
W?
告诉我 上面天气如何 亲爱的?
Tell me something, how's the weather up there, sweetheart?
享受日光浴呢 大麻鬼
Walking on sunshine, toad boy.
看看他们
Look at them.
他们大半不是纯种吸血鬼
Half of these bastards, they're not even purebloods.
我告诉你什么
I tell you what.
我们为什么不杀光它们?
Why don't we just fucking kill everyone?
免得有漏网之鱼
Just to make sure.
好机会 要杀他还不容易
God, it would be so easy.
他瞄准你了
He's got you.
操你
Fuck you.
白昼游侠
Daywalker.
妈妈 饿饿
Mother's milk.
离日出半大约小时 灰姑娘们 动作快
I say we got about half an hour till sunrise, Cinderella. Hurry up.
看到一个但跟丢了
I spotted one, but lost him.
提高警觉
Be on the lookout.
该死
Fuck.
惠斯勒 车顶上有东西
Whistler, man, they're on the roof. On the roof of my bus.
嘘
Shh.
诺玛
Nomak.
白昼游侠
Daywalker.
我招惹你了吗?
What am I to you?
敌人的敌人是朋友还是敌人?
Is the enemy of my enemy my friend or my enemy?
啊!
Aah!
遭受攻击 有三个 可能不只
We're under attack! There's three of them. Probably more.
太阳出来了
Daylight.
什么怪东西?
银弹没用
Silver don't do shit.
不要浪费子弹
Don't waste the bullets.
- 见鬼了  - 听到没有 丘巴?
- Motherfucker.  - You hear me, Chupa?
笑一个
Say "cheese."
下来
Come on.
日光浴吗 王八蛋?
How about some daylight, motherfucker?
丑陋的怪物
该死
Fuck!
你流血了 被咬吗?
背后 背后受伤
听我说 被攻击的话 用紫外光 他们受不了光线
Listen to me. If you're under attack, use your UV lights. They can't take the light.
教士?
Priest?
不能死在这里 加油
We're not dying here, man. Come on.
教士挂了
Priest is down.
日出了 你得孤军奋战 刀锋
Daylight's coming. You're on your own, Blade.
你处心积虑找我 刀锋战士?
You want me so bad, Blade?
我就在这
Here I am.
为什么要杀我?
Why kill me?
你我有共同的敌人
You and I, we have the same enemy.
我们的目标一样
We want the same thing.
我们的需求相同 刀锋
We need the same thing, Blade.
怎么啦?
What happened?
你怎么没说他们...
Why didn't you tell me these things were immune...
- ...对银制品和大蒜免疫?  - 我并不知道
- ...to silver and garlic?  - I didn't know.
如果知道 你会说吗?
If you did, would you have told me?
我想你听到就会知道事实
I think you know the truth when you hear it.
他为什么没把你杀了?
Then why didn't he kill you?
- 他被咬多久了?  - 大约20分钟
- How long since he's been bitten?  - About 20 minutes.
- 他的皮肤滚烫  - 他已经开始蜕变了
- His skin is fucking burning.  - He's already starting to change.
谁来让他住嘴?
Will someone just shut him the fuck up?
杀了我 丘巴!
无惧之人...
等等
Hold on!
- 扶着他 丘巴  - 来吧
- Hold him, Chupa!  - Come on, man.
给他一个痛快吧
Just put him out of his fucking misery.
那样杀不了他
Don't you get it? You can't finish him that way.
按着他 按着他 丘巴
Hold him down. Hold him down, Chupa.
让开
Move.
退后!
Back off!
只有这个绝招 你们麻烦大了
If that was your Bloodpack Sunday punch, we're in trouble.
王八蛋擅离岗位
This motherfucker left his post.
- 他刚失踪了  - 你去哪里?
- He just disappeared.  - Where were you?
我也跟个R异体过了几招
Ran into a little Reaper action myself.
哦 是吗? 过了几招? 我们损失了一个队友 教士
Oh, yeah? How little? We lost a man, Priest.
要我在你胸口刻上他的名字吗
You want me to carve his fucking name on your chest?
我带你们去看
Let me show you.
巷子里有动静于是我就跟过来
Saw it moving in the alley and followed it down.
发现这个状况 我想他们从这儿进出
Found it just like this. I think they came through here.
他想爬回下水道 手臂被卡住
It was trying to crawl back in the culvert and caught his arm.
他像土狼般想咬断自己手臂
Been gnawing at it like a coyote.
可怜的男孩
Little boy blue.
他快死了
It's already dying.
我得尽快检查他
I need to examine it as quickly as possible.
好的 找根杠杆把它撬开
Okay, look for a lever. Let's open it.
他们跟R异体碰上了
They've made contact with the Reapers.
- 有伤亡吗?  - 目前为止一人
- Any casualties?  - One so far.
我相信不是妮莎吧?
It was not Nyssa, I trust?
不是
No.
这是个危险游戏 大马基诺斯
This a dangerous game you're playing, Damaskinos.
刀锋战士暴烈不可测
Blade is too volatile.
你没有办法继续操纵他
You won't be able to keep manipulating him.
你太过担心了
You worry too much.
根据内线通报一切依计划进行
I've been informed by our friend inside that events are unfolding as scripted.
你已经损失一个自己人
You've already lost one of your own.
你愿意牺牲几个?
How many more are you willing to sacrifice?
- 每个都可以牺牲  - 即使是自己的女儿?
- Every one.  - Even your own daughter?
对 即使是她
Yes, even her.
认得这东西吗?
Recognize this?
血库的 他是其中一位警卫
The blood bank. He's one of the guards.
他怎么会死? 为何致命?
So why is he dying? What's killing him?
时间
Time.
新陈代谢太快
His metabolism is burning too fast.
几个小时就需要新鲜的血 不然就开始消耗自己的
They need fresh blood every couple of hours or they'll start feeding on themselves.
诺玛不同 他是带原者
Nomak's different. He's the carrier.
一切从他开始 也由他结束
It all started with him, it'll end with him.
- 把他的嘴打开 飞毛腿  - 嘿
- Open the mouth, Scud.  - Heh.
把他的嘴打开
Open the mouth.
刀兄 别叫我
B, man, come on.
娘娘腔
Sissy.
哦 嘎
Ugh. Gah.
只有舌头会携带病毒
Only the tongue carries the virus.
病毒从倒钩喷射出来
It is injected through these barbs.
咬筋岔成两股
It has bifurcated masseter muscles.
极度发达使咬噬非常有力
Overdeveloped, allowing for a much stronger bite.
颚部结构没有改变
Jaw structure remains the same.
但没有下颚骨
But there's no mandible bone.
压他的牙齿 飞毛腿
Squeeze that tooth, Scud.
神经毒素
Neurotoxin.
用来麻醉受害者
Probably paralyzes their victim while they feed.
大蒜 银制品都拿他没办法
Garlic don't work. Silver, that don't work.
- 只能靠阳光 对吧?  - 但对我们也会致命
- We gotta go with the sunlight, right?  - That's deadly to us too.
想想看有没有其他办法
So let's see what else we can find.
你的伤口好多了
好得相当快
R异体跟我们大不相同 就像我们跟你们不一样
These things are as different from us as we are from you.
看看那个
Look at that.
心脏包藏在骨头里
The heart is encased in bone.
- 只有侧边会受到伤害  - 靠运气才能射穿骨头
- Only the side is vulnerable.  - Good luck getting a stake through that.
拔下的蜘蛛脚会自行走动...
Pull a leg off a spider, it keeps moving on its own...
...没有身体它还是会走路
...essentially trying to walk without a body attached to it.
- 你在干嘛?  - 瞧瞧什么叫杀不死?
- What the fuck are you doing?  - Hardwired, right?
搞什么鬼?
What the fuck is that?
脑部已经死亡 身体还能进食
Brain's dead. Body's still trying to feed.
离天亮还有六小时 事先准备好
We got six hours before sunrise. Be ready by then.
嘿 日出要干嘛?
Hey, what happens at sunrise?
刀锋战士 我在跟你说话 日出要干嘛?
Blade, I'm talking to you. What happens at sunrise?
出去猎杀
We hunt.
- 光天化日之下?  - 你开什么玩笑
- In broad daylight?  - You gotta be fucking joking.
擦点防晒油 温室小花
You better get you some sunscreen, buttercup.
听着 屎蛋
Listen, shitkicker.
没死绝算你他妈好狗运
You're about one cunt hair away from hillbilly heaven.
你说脏话真好听
I love it when you talk dirty.
阳光是我们唯一的武器
Sunlight's the only edge we've got.
- 只有靠它才伤得了他们  - 我们也受不了阳光
- They'll be more vulnerable then.  - And so will we.
面对事实吧
Let's be real about one thing.
我不敢奢望大家平安归来
I don't expect everybody to make it back tomorrow.
记得随时保护自己
Remember to protect yourselves at all times.
你在找什么?
What are you looking for?
磷光棒 如果能够找到光源...
Phosphor rods. If I can suss out the light source...
...或许能做些紫外光手榴弹
...maybe I can make some sort of UV flash-bang grenade or something.
我试过了
It's been tried already.
但你没有飞毛腿的天才
Yeah, but you didn't have the Scudster working on it then, did you?
- 刀锋  - 嗯
- Blade.  - Mm.
- 你跟他们说话的方式  - 怎么样?
- The way you talk to them, us.  - What is it?
我们是队友 记得吧?
We are together in this, remember?
为什么那么恨我们?
Why do you hate us so much?
宿命
It's fate.
- 打从骨子里不喜欢  - 很好 我也一样
- It's in my blood.  - Well, it's in mine too.
我是血统纯正的吸血鬼
I'm a pureblood. I was born a vampire.
你比谁都了解嗜血的感觉 从血液里直奔而出
You know the thirst better than any of us, shooting that serum of yours.
我们唯一的不同 是我早已接受了事实
The only difference between us is that I made peace with what I am a long time ago.
- 你跟刀锋战士认识多久了?  - 快20年了
- How long have you known Blade?  - Going on 20 years.
他不太爱谈过去
He doesn't talk about the old days that much.
他什么事都不太爱说
Blade doesn't talk about anything much.
想听件有趣的事吗?
You want to hear something funny?
刀锋战士把你看成父亲
Blade kind of looks at you like a father figure.
说来听听
Tell me something.
你们怎么认识的?
How'd you two hook up?
我背包旅行
I was backpacking.
有一次徒步旅行碰到两个妓女...
I met these two chicks, decided to take them back to my, uh, tent...
- ...我决定带她们回帐篷玩3P  - 帅哦
- ...for a little Three's Company action.  - Pretty.
哪料到她们开始撕我的腹肌
Next thing I know, Janet and Chrissy start tearing chunks out of my stomach.
刀锋救我一命 自然变成朋友
Blade shows up, saves my ass.
一切都解决了
Everything else just sort of fell into place.
- 试试看  - 好啊
- Let's try it.  - All right.
被你说对了 没屁用
Maybe I fucked up. Maybe you were right.
帅呆了 老爹有样新武器
All right. Papa's got a brand new bag.
我有个问题
Let me ask one question.
到哪找R异体?
How the hell are we gonna find these Reapers?
不必找 他们会送上门来
We won't have to. They'll come to us.
- 什么玩意?  - 费洛蒙
- What is this shit?  - Pheromones.
从R异体肾上腺萃取的
Harvested from the Reapers'adrenal glands.
他们会被吸引过来
They're gonna key to it.
他要我们靠屌臊味诱出R异体?
They want us to spray on some suckpuppy's nut juice?
先用火力逐退他们
First use your firearms to drive them back.
然后丢紫外光手榴弹
Then toss your UV grenades.
这是我们的终极决定版
Right. This is what we got for the grand finale.
我将这玩意连接上硝化甘油
I hot-wired a couple of these babies to a nitro-vaceem.
开火时格外小心 好吗?
Just be real careful where you pop your load, all right?
你呢 你不去?
And you, you're not coming?
不 我爱好和平
No. I'm a lover, not a fighter.
紫外光会延迟10秒
UVs have a 10-second delay.
记得要找掩护
Nyssa, just remember to take cover.
刀锋 帮个忙
Hey, Blade, give me a hand.
你跟那妞倒蛮来电的?
You and Miss Muffet getting a little cozy there?
我如果是你 我不会多管闲事
I wouldn't worry about that if I was you.
我看你搞不清楚...
Looks to me like you're getting confused...
...自己站哪边了
...as to which side of the line you're standing on.
无聊人说无聊话...
Those are real hollow words coming from a man...
...你跟敌人混了两年
...who just spent two years running with the enemy.
这话是什么意思?
And what the hell is that supposed to mean?
你懂的 惠斯勒 有句老话说:
You know, Whistler, there's an old saying:
"亲近朋友 但要更亲近敌人"
"Keep your friends close, but keep your enemies closer."
希望你记住这句话
You might want to remember that.
刀锋 我们应该分成三组
Blade, we should split into three units.
我们要引诱 不是吓跑他们
We're trying to attract them, not scare them off.
有人在黑暗里看不见 秃子
Yeah, well, some of us can't see in the dark, you fucking nipplehead.
我该怎么办?
What am I supposed to do?
带老花眼镜啊 阿公 跟好
Bifocals, Grandpa, and try to keep up.
光斧
我们动手
Let's do this.
嘿 乡巴佬
Hey, hillbilly.
你想干嘛?
What the fuck you doing?
这里四下无人呢 温室小花
Ain't nobody here but you and us, buttercup.
我们挂了个战友 刀锋战士也得挂一个
We lose a partner, and Blade loses one!
我让你们两个相亲相爱一下
I'll leave you two lovebirds some time to yourselves.
魏莲?
Verlaine?
(10秒自动引爆器)
东地道里发现一群R异体
I spotted a group in the east tunnel.
我正在设定炸弹
I'm prepping the bomb pack.
妮莎
Nyssa.
出来!
Get out!
快点
Right now.
不!
No!
我把他们引过来 照我的话做 快!
I'll attract them to me. Do what I tell you. Move!
10秒...
Ten...
...9秒...
...nine...
...8秒...
...eight...
...7秒...
...seven...
...6秒...
...Six...
...5秒...
...five...
...4秒...
...four...
...3秒...
...three...
...2秒...
...two...
...1秒
...one.
雷哈特... 招集组员!
烂东西
Piece of junk.
丘巴
...马上离开那里!
这是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is this?
你想臭死我啊 老头?
You trying to stink me to death, old man?
丘巴
马上离开那里!
等等
Wait!
- 你还好吧?  - 没事
- You okay?  - Yeah.
快走 来了一大票
We gotta move. We got a lot of company.
各单位集合 集合!
All units, regroup. Regroup!
吃屎吧 丑巴怪!
Eat shit, you ugly motherfuckers!
那里没有人了!
There's nobody left!
啊
Aah! Unh.
- 炸药包呢?  - 我不得不丢在那边地道里
- Where's the bomb pack?  - Had to leave it down that tunnel.
剩下的费洛蒙给我
Give me the rest of the pheromones.
进那条地道去 快 快 快!
Go down that tunnel. Go, go, go!
你们显然搞不清楚你们惹上了谁!
You obviously do not know who you are fucking with!
刀锋战士 我有没有告诉你炸弹的控制杆卡住了?
By the way, Blade, did I happen to mention the bomb lever is stuck?
吃个够吧!
Suck this!
走!
Let's go!
想咬我吗? 很好 来啊!
You want a bite of me? Well, come on!
来啊 孬种!
Come on, motherfucker!
惠斯勒
Whistler.
等等
Wait.
我会饶你一命...
You will survive this...
...让你转告刀锋战士...
...only to tell Blade...
...关于这枚戒指
...about this ring.
以及事实的真相 真相 老头
About the truth. The truth, old man.
大马基诺斯
Damaskinos.
妮莎
Nyssa.
干得漂亮
You've done a great job.
我该说 不太漂亮吧
Not that great, I'd say.
怎么啦 女儿?
What is it, my daughter?
我让你脸上无光爸爸...
我害家族蒙羞
刀锋战士救了我
他是个可敬的勇士
我知道
他还活着吗?
武器被他们拿走了 所有武器 包括你的剑
They took them. All our weapons. Even your sword.
里面有人不断通风报信
Somebody's been keeping tabs on us from inside.
这是哪里?
Where are we?
他们巢穴里的一个密室
Some kind of chamber deep in their lair.
我们的工作站全被他们毁了
They smashed up everything, the workshop, all of it.
我们从一开始就被骗
They've been lying to us from day one.
R异体家族并不会演化
The Reaper strain didn't evolve.
这是个骗局
It was designed.
- 什么?  - 我们被设计了 诺玛说的
- What?  - Designed. Nomak told me.
在下水道里碰到他 他饶了我一命
I saw him back in the sewers. He let me live.
是吗?
Did he?
他还真大方
How generous of him.
我带你来看辉煌的战果
I brought you here to see the fruits of our labor.
多年来 我努力不懈 为了去除遗传上的弱点
For years I've struggled to rid our kind of any hereditary weaknesses.
发现重组DNA 是唯一可行的一条路
And so recombining DNA was simply the next logical step.
诺玛是第一个试验品 瑕疵品
Nomak was the first. A failure.
但 不久 将有纯正的新品种...
But in time, there will be a new pure race...
...来自我们自己的血肉...
...begotten from my own flesh...
...对银制品免疫...
...immune to silver...
...很快 甚至无惧阳光
...soon even sunlight.
我有个问题 大骗子
I got a question for you, you lying son of a bitch.
诺玛怎会有这枚戒指?
You want to explain how Nomak got ahold of this ring?
事到如今还不清楚
I would have thought that was obvious at this point.
我给他的，父亲给儿子的礼物
I gave it to him, of course. A gift from father to son.
我以为他不会逃走
I thought he'd never leave.
狼跟绵羊和平相处太久了
The wolf has lain with the sheep long enough.
雷哈特 该说拜拜啦
Reinhardt, you can kiss your ass goodbye.
对不起 老兄
Oh, huh. I'm sorry, man.
别浪费时间 那是枚哑弹
B, you're wasting your time, man. The bomb's a dud.
根本不会爆
It was never supposed to explode.
只是让你吓人的
It was just supposed to make you feel in control.
你以为我被你吃定了 老大?
You thought you had me on a short leash, didn't you, jefe?
舒服多了
Much better.
看到没?
See this?
我是大马基诺斯家族成员
I'm one of Damaskinos'familiars.
他们要我带你来搞定诺玛
They needed my help to bring you here to control Nomak.
老废物只是个饵
The old fuck, he was always just bait.
看看他 他就是你真正的弱点
I mean, look at him. He's your only real weakness, man.
不管你再迅速 强悍...
You may be fast, you may be strong and all that other bullshit...
...但终究 刀兄 你太有人性
...but in the end, B, you're just too human.
而你是块废料
Well, you little shit.
- 嘿  - 啊
- Heh.  - Unh.
你以为他们破解了保全系统?
You think they scoped out my security system?
我放他们进来的 笨蛋!
I let them in, asshole!
我根本是拿钥匙给他们
I practically handed them the keys.
你听到光头说的吧?
You heard Cue Ball, right?
很快他们也成白昼游侠了
Pretty soon they're all gonna be daywalkers, man.
我宁可当宠物也不要当食物
When that happens, I'd rather be a pet than cattle.
懂了吗 老刀?
You got me, B?
- 你有什么高见?  - 两件事
- What do you think about that, man?  - Two things.
第一 从你被招降开始 我就一清二楚
One, I've been onto you since they turned you.
第二...
And two...
...那不是枚哑弹
...it's not a dud.
靠 帅毙了
Oh, great.
我才刚开始喜欢他说
I was just starting to like him.
把他干掉
Take him down!
我们会善用你每一滴血
We're going to harvest your blood, every drop of it.
然后 骨髓 器官无一遗漏
Then bone marrow, organs, everything.
找出成为白昼游侠的关键
We'll find the missing key to creating daywalkers.
现在 会有点痛哦
Now, this might hurt a bit.
漂亮
Nice.
我想知道...
I wonder...
...他用它杀了多少吸血鬼
...how many vampires he's killed with this thing.
还不够多 奥国猪
Not nearly enough, Fritz.
继续耍嘴皮子 老粗
Keep talking, honky-tonk.
送你上西天时 我会让你舒畅无比
Just makes my sending you to the next world all the sweeter.
唬谁 看多了
Been there, done thet.
越狠越好 孬种 帐我们慢慢再算
Do your worst, chickenshit. We'll settle up after.
还有什么我不知道的?
What else should I find out?
我完全信赖你...
I trusted you...
...我的手下...
...with my men...
...我的意志...
...with my will...
...以及我的生命
...with my life.
你 叫我们出生入死
You, you sent us out there.
叫我们替你卖命
You sent me to die.
我们的敌人救了我两次 你却在利用我...
Our enemy saved my life twice, and you have used us...
...利用自己的骨肉
...your own children.
说得没错 妮莎
Make no mistake, Nyssa.
在我们种族里 跟权势相比...
Those blood ties mean nothing to me...
...骨肉之亲算得了什么
...when measured against the ascendancy of our race.
你以为上帝会眷顾谁?
Who do you think God really favors in the web?
蜘蛛还是落网的苍蝇?
The spider or the fly?
- 诺玛  - 嗯?
- Nomak.  - Hmm?
他怎么样?
What about him?
他想要复仇...
He wants revenge...
...针对他的创造者
...on the people who created him.
你说的可能没错
You may be right.
可惜他不知道这个地方
But fortunately for us, he doesn't know this location.
现在...
Now...
...他知道了
...he does.
搞什么鬼?
What the fuck?
振作 当着我的面你别想死
Come on, kid. Don't you even think about dying on me.
你没放弃过我 我不会放弃你
You didn't give up on me, I won't give up on you.
振作点 刀锋
Come on, Blade.
血
Blood.
对
Yeah.
血
Blood.
爸爸
Father!
他进不来的
He'll never enter here.
爸爸
Father!
加油 孩子
Go on, kid.
走
Go!
干掉他!
Go! Get him!
过去杀他!
Get in there!
恩
Hmm.
很好 就像我爸杀我妈时说的:
Well, like my daddy said right before he killed my mom:
"想搞得定 非亲自动手不可"
"Want anything done right, you gotta do it yourself."
他还说…
He also said...
你会不会脸红?
Can you blush?
接着 小伙子
Hey, kid.
我重设了密码
I reset the security code.
- 我们被锁住了  - 你疯了?
- We're locked in.  - Are you insane?
- 我们两个都会没命  - 对
- He'll kill us both.  - Yes.
悲哀吧 不是死在敌人之手...
Isn't it sad that you die not by the hand of your enemy...
...却死在自己子女手中?
...but by that of your own children?
爸爸
Father.
发生在你身上的事
是桩可怕的悲剧
是个不能原谅的错误
但你却回来纠缠不清
我们会找到解药的
让你重享应有的地位
让你重享应有的地位 我们一起征服世界
如果你说的是实话
为什么声音会颤抖?
爸爸
我让你死 不用受我这种苦
经由这个伤口 你的生命得以流传
妮莎
Nyssa.
哥哥 杀了我
断绝这个家族
你...
你是他最钟爱的
诺玛
Nomak!
刀锋 可以在此作个总结
Blade, it could end right here.
你认为呢?
What do you think, huh?
还没结束呢 看来得由我完成父亲的工作
After all, it looks like I've finished my father's job.
好奇怪
It's strange.
痛…
It hurts...
痛苦不见了
It hurts no more.
要不了多久的
It won't be long.
我已经感觉体内的灼热了
I can already feel it burning inside of me.
趁我还是吸血鬼时我想死
I want to die while I'm still a vampire.
我想看看太阳
I want to see the sun.
(伦敦)
3号亭 好好爽一爽
Go to booth number three. Enjoy, man.
女孩是"真"的吗?
Are you sure, uh, that the girls are live?
- 刚检查过  - 谢啦
- Last time I checked.  - Thank you.
剃刀带着 以备不时之需
A couple of razor blades, just in case.
你以为我忘掉你了吗?
Oh, you didn't think I forgot about you, did you?